来尝尝  鲁尼女士
Here you go, Mrs. Rooney.
我烤制了新鲜的松饼
I baked fresh muffins.
我的哥们埃文真是个好客人
My buddy Evan is the perfect houseguest.
他自己整理床铺  他帮着拿报纸
He makes his bed. He gets the paper.
他还会烤松饼
He bakes fresh muffins.
简直是太周到了
He's just so thoughtful,
而且干活的时候满是雀斑的小脸上堆满了笑容
and does it all with a smile on that sweet, freckly face.
他让我看起来糟透了
He's really making me look bad.
好的  谢谢你  埃文
Well, thank you, Evan.
我还没习惯这么贴心的照顾
I am not used to all this attention.
咳咳
Ahem.
长命百岁
Bless you?
我太谢谢你们能在我妈出去开会的时候让我住在这儿了
I really appreciate you letting me stay here while my mom's at a convention.
为什么不休息一下  等我把这里收拾干净呢
Why don't you take a few minutes for yourself and I'll clean up here?
你简直是个小天使啊
You are like a dream.
帕克  你也该从你朋友那里学到些什么了吧
Parker, you could learn a little something from your friend.
伙计  我们要谈谈
Dude, we gotta talk.
太棒了  我妈说谈话时给精神减负的最好方法
Great! My mom says talking is the best way to unburden your soul.
我理解你想多帮帮忙的心情  但是你给我妈做的事越多
I totally get you're trying to be helpful, but the more you do for my mom,
她对我的期望值就越大
the more she'll expect from me.
我现在生活过得这么舒坦
I got a good thing going here.
我绝不需要你插一脚来毁掉了它
And I don't need you waltzing in and ruining it!
我妈说帮人做事就像是释放光芒
My mom says being helpful is a ray of light
我可以以此照亮温馨的小家
I can just shine on our happy home.
那是假话
Not true.
她这么说是想在家务活上偷懒呢
The goal is to get out of chores.
噗
Pfft.
帕克  你真逗啊
Parker, you're hilarious.
哦  等等  你是认真的么
Oh, wait, you're serious?
如果你的父母认为你干什么事都干不成
If your parents think that you're not capable of doing anything,
你就不需要做任何家务活了
you'll never have to do another chore again.
那个世界难道存在么
Does such a world exist?!
确实存在
It does.
让我来教你一套方法
Let me show you a way.
更好的方法
A better way.
帕克的方法
The Parker way.